(カカシ)では 作戦を開始する。
All right, let's begin.
全員 配置につけ。
Everyone, in your positions!
散！
Let's go!
(シズネ)さぁ 私たちも始めるわよ。
Well, we'll get started too!
(キバ)なに
しょぼくれたツラしてんだよ。
Why do you look so depressed?
Huh?
(リー)べつに
しょぼくれてなんか…。
I'm not depressed...
ただ 晶遁使いという
凄腕の忍と戦うチームに➡
Just disappointed that
I'm not on the team
that's going to battle
this amazing Crystal Style user.
入れなかったのが
残念なだけです。
おいおい
オレら もう中忍だぜ。
Hey hey... We're Chunin now.
強いのとやりたいって
気持もわかるが➡
I understand you wanting
to fight someone strong,
わがまま言ってる場合じゃねえぜ。
but this isn't the time to be selfish.
それによ
晶遁使いの手下の連中だって➡
And besides,
her henchmen are ridiculously strong too.
とんでもねえヤツらばっかなんだぜ。
本当ですか!?
Really?
もっと もっと詳しく
お願いします。
Please tell me all the details!
おう…。
これがまた厄介なヤツらでよ。
Y-Yeah sure.
They were a ton of trouble...
(テンテン)私にも聞かせて。
あぁ。
Can I listen in?
Sure... Anyway, they lay a smoke screen,
which is a real pain.
とにかく 面倒なのは
ヤツらの使う煙幕だ。
(リー)煙幕ですか？
毒ですか？ それとも まさか…。
A smoke screen?
Is it toxic? Or...
(キバ)まぁ 最後まで聞けって。
Just listen until the end.
Then will you just get on with it?
(テンテン)なに
もったいぶってんのよ。
(ナルト)ん？
あぁ そっか
お前ら 初対面か。
Oh, right.
You two have never met before.
(シノ)よく気づいたものだな
ナルト。
Sharp of you to notice, Naruto.
こっちは サイっていうんだ。
This here is Sai.
暗部出身で
陰気で空気を読めねえってか➡
He came from the Anbu Black Ops
and he's sorta gloomy and depressing...
人間味に欠けるっちゅうか➡
like he's missing something...
本ばっか読んでる変なヤツ。
(サイ)ナルト…。
Just a weird guy who's
constantly reading books.
Naruto...
でも 絵がうまい。
But he draws great!
それに なかなか強いんだぜ。
And he's pretty strong!
で こっちは シノ
えっと シノは…。
And this guy is Shino.
Umm... Shino is...
シノだってばよ。
well, Shino.
(サイ)油女シノ君だよね？
You're Aburame Shino.
油女シビさんの息子で
戦闘 防御 探索 捕獲➡
You're the son of Aburame Shibi.
You have participated in
numerous missions
relying on your skill in combat,
as a bodyguard, and in search and seizure.
あらゆる任務に対応する➡
万能にして有能な寄壊蟲を操る
秘伝術のスペシャリストだよね。
You're a specialist in the Secret Jutsu
of manipulating Parasitic Insects.
Right?
なんだよ サイ
お前 ずいぶん詳しく知ってんな。
Hey, Sai. How come you know so much?
よく調べたものだな。
You've done your research.
But I guess that goes without saying.
だが それは 当然というべきか。
なぜなら 彼は 元暗部だからだ。
After all, you're a former
Anbu Black Ops member.
ふ～ん まぁ これで
お互いのことはわかったし➡
Well, now that you know each other,
we can be a team.
チームとしてやっていけるわけだ。
ナルト オレの好きな食べものは➡
Naruto.
My favorite foods are wild grass salad
and winter melon.
野草サラダと冬瓜だ。
は？
Huh?
嫌いな食べものは
においの強いものだな。
I don't like...
foods that have a strong odor.
なるほど。
だから何だってんだ？
I see.
So what of it?
同じチームとして 仲間のことは
知っておいたほうがいいだろう。
Since we're on the same team,
we should know about each other.
それが チームワークにつながるからだ。
シノ…。
It affects our teamwork.
Shino...
べつに メシの好みなんて
どうだっていいってばよ。
It really doesn't matter
what kind of foods you like.
えっ!? な なんだ？
Wh-What?
ナルト お前は もっと
オレのことを知る必要がある。
Naruto... You really need to
know more about me.
なぜなら 旧友よりも
新たな仲間のほうが➡
Because it would be strange
if a newcomer knows more
about me than an old friend.
オレのことに詳しいのは
おかしなことだからな。
あ… ハハハ。
やっぱり オレ
お前ら 苦手だってばよ。
I guess I'm just not on
the same wavelength as you guys.
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Four-Corner Sealing Barrier
(紅蓮)牛頭。
Gozu...
(牛頭)へい。
カブトのヤツを どう思う？
Yes?
What do you think about Kabuto?
どうも気に入らないんだよ 私は。
I just don't like the guy...
まあ いいさ。
Well, forget it.
木ノ葉をやった後で
アイツの尻尾をつかんで…。
After I get rid of the Leaf,
I can grab his ponytail and...
((カブト : 幽鬼丸は 三尾を
操作するためだけの道具))
Yuukimaru is simply a tool
to control the Three-Tails.
なんだってんだ！ このイライラは！
Why the hell am I feeling
so irritated! Damn it!
クソッ!!
行くよ！
Let's go!
自分は 紅蓮さんに
ついて行きます。
I will accompany you,
no matter where you go...
どこへでも。
(濡羅吏)出ても 大丈夫。
It's all clear.
(鬼霧)チッ ズブ濡れだぜ。
Damn! I'm soaking wet!
濡れないお前は いいよな 濡羅吏。
You're lucky you don't get wet, Nurari!
うん？ 何だ それ テメエのペットか？
What is that? Your pet?
ごくろうさま。
Good work.
(鬼鳳)さて 今回も
いつもの作戦でいきますかい？
All right... Shall we go
with the usual strategy?
アニキ？
Bro...?
Huh?
(鱗児)そうだな。
いつもどおりでいこう。
Yeah... Let's do it the usual way.
これから行うのは
結界四方封陣というもの。
We will proceed with
the Four-Corner Sealing Barrier.
まず 三尾を探し当て
続いて 封印術へと移行する。
First, we'll locate the Three-Tails
and then move on to the Sealing Jutsu.
印は さっき教えたとおり。
いくわよ！
I've already shown you
the hand signs. Ready?
結界四方封陣 探！
Four-Corner Sealing Barrier... Search!
よし
このまま術式を持ち上げるわよ！
All right, let's go right
into the Jutsu.
はっ！
はあ ひとまず
これでいいわ。
This should do for now.
このチャクラバランスを保ったまま
徐々に 間隔を広げていく。
We'll maintain this Chakra balance,
and slowly enlarge the opening.
結界の下に
三尾が入れば反応が出るはず。
If the Three-Tails is
below the barrier,
we'll get a reaction.
いくわよ。
(サクラ)ちょっと待ってください！
Ready?
Please wait a minute!
こんな繊細な
チャクラコントロールを続けていたら➡
If we continue with
such delicate Chakra Control...
敵が現れても対処できません。
and the enemy appears...
We won't be able to oppose them.
(シズネ)対処しなくていい。
えっ？
We won't have to fight back.
Huh?!
あなたたちは
チャクラコントロールにのみ集中するの。
You just concentrate on
your Chakra Control.
敵のことは 仲間を信じればいい。
And believe that your comrades
will take care of the enemy.
わかりました。
I understand.
いの！ 大丈夫？
- Ino!
- Oh!
Are you all right?!
《いの :
敵を警戒するどころじゃない。
How can I stay alert for the enemy?
こんな チャクラコントロールを
続けられるわけが…》
I don't even know if I can maintain
this level of Chakra Control...
大丈夫よ いの。
You'll be fine, Ino.
アンタならやれる。
サクラ。
I know you can do this...
Sakura...
チャクラコントロールは
私たちの基本。 でしょ？
Chakra Control is basic to us, right?
((サクラ : 大丈夫よ いの。
You'll be fine, Ino!
アンタならできるって。
You can do it,
I'm telling you!
チャクラコントロールは
医療忍術の基礎中の基礎よ。
Chakra Control is the foundation
of Medical Ninjutsu.
さっ もう一度。
Now, let's try again.
(もっと間隔を一定に
もっと繊細に 緻密に))
Get a fix on the opening!
Gently... Keep it very fine...
(サクラ)
アンタだって 努力してきたんだから。
You've persevered too...
ハッ バカにしないでよね このくらい。
Hah, don't belittle me!
Of course, I...
できて当然よ！
can do this!
わかったって オメエ何が。
You got it? What do you-?
もちろん 敵の攻略法です。
The strategy to capture
the enemy, of course!
さっきも言っただろ。
Like I told you earlier...
あの煙幕の中じゃ
視界はほとんどゼロだ。
In that smoke screen,
visibility is almost zero...
悔しいが 赤丸の鼻もきかねえ！
And as much as I hate to admit it,
even Akamaru's nose is useless...
だが敵は その煙幕の中でも
こちらの位置がわかり➡
Yet the enemy knows our position
and keeps attacking...
連続攻撃をしかけてくる。
基本的には 煙幕の中での戦闘を
避けるってのが セオリーだろうが。
Basically, we should avoid fighting
inside the smoke screen, but...
ダメです！ それでは敵から
逃げながら戦うことになり➡
No!
That's just running away
from the enemy,
敵を倒すのは 難しいでしょう。
and will only make it harder
to defeat them.
だから 厄介な敵だって。
That's why I said they're a nuisance--
その方法が
わかったと言ったんです！
And I'm saying I figured out a way!
(テンテン)へぇ～ リーも中忍になって➡
Lee, now that you're a Chunin,
you're using your brain as well.
少しは頭を使うようになったのね。
ただの修業バカじゃなかったんだ。
You're not just a workout addict.
(ヤマト)たいしたもんだね。 その方法
聞かせてもらえないかい？
Good job...
Well then, why don't you tell us your plan?
はい。 その攻略法とは。
All right, the strategy is...
(２人)その攻略法とは？
- The strategy is...?
攻略法とは。
とは？
The strategy is...
それは…。
Is...?
It's...
ガッツです！ ガッツで当たれば➡
Guts! If we have the guts,
there's no enemy we can't beat!
倒せない敵なんて ありません！
って あれ？
皆さんどうしたんです？
Huh?
What's the matter, everyone?
テメエ！
散々もったいつけやがって➡
Why you--!
Keeping us in suspense!
何だそりゃ！ ざけんじゃねえぞ！
And that's all you have?
何です。
ボクが何をしたと言うんです？
- Quit fooling around!
- Wh-What?
What did I do?!
ダメだ やっぱただの修業バカだ。
I take it back.
He's just a workout addict, after all.
よし 行くぞ！
ああ。
All right! Let's go!
シノ そっちはどうだ？
Right...
もう少し時間がかかる。
Shino, how's it going over there?
I need a little more time...
わかった。
サイ 基本的なフォーメーションは➡
All right...
Sai. Basically, we'll keep
the same formation...
ヤマトが隊長を務めたときと
同じだと思っていい。
that Yamato used when he was captain.
はい 先輩。
ん？ あぁ…。
Yes... Senpai.
お前も あっちの出だったな。
あっちって？
Huh? Oh right.
You also came from there.
Huh? There?
暗部だよ。
まぁ あっちの戦い方じゃ➡
Anbu Black Ops.
The way they fight,
仲間を守るなんて方程式は
ないだろうが。
they have no protocol to protect
their comrades.
今回は仲間の一撃を
最大限に活かすための戦いだ。
But this time, we're fighting to protect
our comrades at all cost.
そこんところは くれぐれも…。
大丈夫ですよ。
I want you to keep that in mind...
ん？
仲間を信じる力。
Don't worry.
ボクは それを信じて
今ここにいるんですから。
Having faith in my comrades...
I'm here because
that's something I believe in now.
ヘッ！
オメエも わかってきたじゃねえか。
Hey, you're beginning to understand...
((自来也 :
思っているヤツがいる所が➡
The place where someone
thinks of you,
(帰ってくる所だって
言うからのぅ))
that's the place you go back to...
《そうだ 仲間が思ってくれるから
そこに帰れるんだ。
That's right.
There are friends thinking of you.
信じてる仲間がいるから
そこに…》
That's why you can return to them...
Friends who have faith in you...
((幽鬼丸 : やっと帰る場所が
見つかったんだよ。
I finally found the place...
where I can go back to.
(ね！ 紅蓮さん))
Right, Guren-san?
《アイツは まだ➡
本当に自分のことを
思ってくれるってことが➡
He still doesn't understand the true
meaning of thinking about someone.
わかってねえんだ。
アイツに騙されて…》
(カカシ)来るぞ！
She is tricking him...
They're coming!
とにかく シノから離れて…。
Anyway, I need to keep
my distance from Shino...
今度は逃がしゃしないよ。
You won't get away this time.
テメエ！
Why you--!
((ボク やっと帰る場所が
見つかったんだよ))
I finally found the place
where I can go back to.
テメエが幽鬼丸を
仲間だと騙したんだ！
You've tricked Yuukimaru into
believing you're a friend!
うるさい！
Shut up!
あまい！
Too easy!
ナルト！
Naruto!
始まったか。
こっちも来るぞ！
It's begun...
Here they come!
ヤマト隊長 煙幕の野郎だぜ！
Captain Yamato!
It's the smoke-screen guy!
《アイツが先兵か。 ならば…》
So he's the vanguard...
Well then...!
あっ！
(リー)ナイスです ヤマト隊長！
Nice, Captain Yamato!
待て リー！
木ノ葉烈風！
Wait, Lee!
Leaf... Whirlwind!
何です!?
あっ！
What?
くらえ 滅臭煙牢！
Eat this! Vanishing Smoke Prison!
まずい…。
いわんこっちゃねえ！
- This is bad...
- I told you!
(テンテン)リーの援護に向かうわ！
(ヤマト)ダメだ 相打ちの可能性がある。
I'm going to backup Lee!
No! You may end up
attacking each other...
《これが
キバ君の言っていた煙幕…。
This is the smoke screen
Kiba-kun talked about...
なるほど
ちょっと先も見えそうにない。
He was right.
I can't see in front of me. Then...
ならば…》
(鬼鳳)鱗児さん。
こっちは いつでもオーケーですぜ。
Rinji-san, we're ready anytime.
How's his position?
ヤツの位置は？ 鱗児さん？
オレには やるべきことができた。
Rinji-san?
えぇ!? ちょっ 鱗児さん!?
There's something I must do...
Huh? Hey, Rinji-san?
《クッ！ 相手の気配が
まったくわからない。
I can't sense anyone's presence...
煙の範囲は みんなも巻き込まれて
いるんでしょうか。
How far does the smoke spread?
Is everyone else caught up in it?
クッ どうすれば!?》
((ガイ : リーよ。
What should I do?
(ガイ)忍びたるもの➡
Lee...
例え 五感のすべてを
奪われようとも➡
A Ninja never gives up,
even if all his senses are shut down.
諦めてはならぬ。
はい ガイ先生！
つらい修業の日々を思い出せば
こんなのは些細なことだ。
Yes, Guy-sensei...
If you recall your days of harsh training,
this is nothing.
オレたちには五感を超えた
心の目がある！
We have something stronger
than the five senses,
《心の目!?》
the vision of the heart.
そうだ！ たゆまぬ努力と根性で
手に入れた➡
The vision of the heart...
Right!
Seize the enemy with
your Spirit sensor
(ガッツセンサーで敵を捉えるのだ！))
which you developed through
unceasing diligence and determination!
《リー : ガッツセンサー！
おぉ～っ！
ナイスネーミングです ガイ先生！
Spirit sensor!
Wise words, Guy-sensei!
よ～し ガッツセンサー オン！》
All right! Spirit sensor... On!
(鬼鳳)鱗児さん 作戦変更なんて
聞いてないっすよ！
Rinji! How can you change
the strategy now?!
ガッツセンサーに反応ありです！
I've got something through
my Spirit sensor!
鱗児さんの能力なしじゃ
この作戦は…。
Without Rinji's power,
this strategy won't...
うわっ！
何！ 何なの!?
どうした鬼鳳!? おい！
What? What is that?
What happened, Kihou?! Hey!
クッ クソッ！ どこだ!?
Damn... Where the hell is he...?
うっ!!
影舞葉！ 木ノ葉大旋風！
(キバ)やったぜ！
Shadow Dance!
Severe Leaf Hurricane!
これで終わりです！
He did it!
It's over!
あの野郎 心配かけやがって！
(赤丸)ワンワン！
That guy! Making us worry.
って ことは！
今なら あの煙幕のなかは
敵だけってことよね。
That means...
Only the enemy is in
that smoke screen now.
操昇竜！
Rising Dragon Control!
ハッ!!
どうなってんだよ!?
What's going on?!
ヒィ～!!
チクショウ！ これじゃ
まるっきり立場が逆だぜ！
Damn it!
Our positions are totally reversed!
こんな煙幕
さっさと取っ払っちまいなよ！
Just get rid of
this damned smoke screen!
ヒィ!!
まだまだ ハッ！
It's not over yet...
確かにこれじゃ
見えないほうが不利だな。
Right now,
it's worse if we can't see.
(濡羅吏/鬼霧)グワーッ!!
ど どうなってんだ!?
Wh-What's happening?
Were these guys this weak?
コイツら こんな弱かったのか!?
(テンテン)どうってことない連中ね。
They're not much, these guys.
(リー)もう少し やりがいがあると
思ったんですが。
I expected more of a fight.
《このままじゃ➡
オレが ダメ忍者扱い
されちまうじゃねえか！》
If this keeps up,
I'll be treated like a useless Ninja.
((晶遁使いの手下の連中だって➡
And besides, her henchmen
are ridiculously strong too.
(とんでもねえヤツらばっか
なんだぜ！))
こうしちゃいられねえぞ 赤丸。
ワン！
We can't stay like this, Akamaru...
うお～っ!!
や… やばい！
逃げるぞ！
赤丸！
ワン！
- Th-This is bad!
- Let's run!
Akamaru!
(キバ)ダイナミック マーキング！
Dynamic Marking!
うわ～っ！
何よ これ？ 臭い！
ニオイなら消してやる。 減臭煙牢！
Wh-What is this?! It stinks!
I can erase the smell!
Vanishing Smoke Prison!
いったん退くぞ！
Everyone, retreat!
なぜ オレたちの位置がわかる？
赤丸のダイナミック マーキングは特別だ。
How did you know our position?!
Akamaru's Dynamic Marking is special.
テメエのガスでも ニオイは消せねえ。
Even your gas cannot eliminate the smell.
テメエらには コケにされたぜ…。
くらえ!!
You guys made a fool out of me...
Eat this!
(みんな)うわ～っ！
(キバ)牙通牙！
Fang Over Fang!
(みんな)うわ～っ！
へっ！
(リー)やりましたね！
(テンテン)やったわね！
なんと まあ…
ボクの出る幕は なかったようだね。
You did it!
- We did it!
- Oh well...
It seems there was role for me to play.
《こっちは 晶遁使いに
戦力を集中させないための陽動…。
I was a diversion so that
he couldn't accumulate fighting power...
カカシ先輩の読みは正しかった。
Kakashi Senpai read
the situation perfectly.
だが 対晶遁班… 果たして…》
But this Crystal Style Counter team...
(牛頭)うお～っ!!
ふん！
くるぞ！
多重影分身の術！
They're coming!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
ザコは 引っ込んでな！
The small fry can stay out of this!
うお～っ！
はっ！
カカシ先生！
全力で きな！ 写輪眼のカカシ！
Kakashi Sensei!
Come at me with all your might!
Sharingan Kakashi!
あいにく オレは
熱血派じゃないんでね。
Unfortunately,
I'm not the hot-blooded type.
幽鬼丸を どこへ隠した！
Where'd you hide Yuukimaru?!
お前には関係ない。
アイツは オレのせいで➡
That's none of your business!
お前らのところに
行っちまったんだ。
It's my fault that he went over
to you guys!
アイツを 道具みてえに使うのは
許せねえ!!
I won't let you use him
like some kind of tool!
オレは お前を倒して
幽鬼丸を助ける！
I'm gonna beat you
and rescue Yuukimaru!
(紅蓮)黙れ！
キサマに何がわかるってんだ!!
Shut up!
As if... you understand!
クソ！ クソ！
Damn! Damn it!
《まだか…》
Not yet?
コイツらは 普通の寄壊蟲よりも
多くのチャクラを必要とする。
These guys require more Chakra
than the usual Parasitic Insects.
なぜなら 晶遁使いのアイツを
倒すためだ！
And that's...
in order to bring down
the Crystal Style user!
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
Next Episode
That was really close.
So, are they ready?
(ヒナタ)お待たせ！
If they weren't, I wouldn't have come.
Humph... If it isn't the Insect user.
ヒナタ また シナモンロール食ったのか？
Your Jutsu is useless against me.
な… なんで わかったの？
(キバ)最近 オレの鼻 ムチャクチャ
きくようになってきてよ。
Your Jutsu won't work against me.
And that's because my insects are
now resistant to your Crystal Style.
そ… そうなんだ すごいね キバ君！
What?!
(キバ)それが いいことばかりじゃ
ねえんだよな！
Now the tables have turned.
Get ready.
I won't let you get away now!
悩みがあるなら聞いてやろう。
なぜなら…。
Breaking the
Crystal Style
Next time: "Breaking the Crystal Style"
(キバ)実際 そのせいで
いろいろ支障があってよ➡
街を歩きゃ 香水のにおいで
気持悪くなっちまうし➡
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hinata, have you been eating
cinnamon rolls again?
数キロ離れた焼肉屋のにおいで
腹は減るし…。
H-How do you know?
まあ 優秀すぎる能力ってのは
諸刃の剣だな！
My sense of smell has become
outrageously keen lately.
天才ならではの
悩みっつうかよ！
I-Is that so?
You're amazing, Kiba-kun.
(シノ)キバ！
But that's not always a good thing.
ぐあっ… これは！
If something's troubling you,
you can talk to me.
くさやだ さっき
無視された お返しだ。
- That's what a team is for...
- In fact, it's caused me some problems.
テ… テメエ。
When walking around town,
the smell of perfume makes me nauseous...
キバ君 大丈夫!?
意外なところに
弱点があったものだ。
A barbecue place could be
several kilometers away,
but the smell makes me hungry...
Anyway, possessing a superior power
is like a double-edged sword.
Other geniuses can
understand this problem...
Kiba...
Huh?
That's...!
It's a kusaya. My payback for
the way you ignored me earlier.
Wh-Why you...!
K-Kiba-kun, are you alright?
I found a weakness
in the most unexpected place.